fxarena.com 2016-09-28

# 

  Your Privacy is Our Priority
  Genius Trading Ltd (“FXARENA”), a Belize registered company under company number 150338
  (5 Cork Street, Belize City, Belize), is committed to safeguarding all personal information provided
  to us by our valued customers. This Privacy Policy describes how we handle and protect personal
  information we collect from individuals who apply for, or receive, our products and services. The
  provisions of this notice apply to former as well as current customers.
  Why and How We Collect Personal Information:
  When you apply for, or maintain, an account with Genius Trading Ltd, we collect personal
  information about you for business purposes, such as evaluating your financial needs, processing
  your requests and transactions, informing you about products and services that may be of interest
  to you, and providing customer service.
  The personal information we collect includes:
 Information you provide to us on applications and other forms, such as your name, address, date
  of birth and occupation.
 Information about your transactions with us.
 Information you provide to us to verify your identity, such as a passport, or received from other
  entities not affiliated with Genius Trading Ltd.
  Sharing Information:
  We may share personal information described above for business purposes, such as servicing
  customer accounts and informing customers about new products and services, as permitted by
  applicable law. The information we share for marketing purposes is limited by the information
  described above, such as name, address and account information.
                                                                                                     2

Sharing Information:
In order to support the financial products and services we provide to you, we may share the
personal information described above with third party service providers and joint marketers, not
affiliated with us, including:
Financial service institutions (e.g., advisers, dealers, brokers, trust companies and banks) with
whom we have joint marketing agreements, such as agreements to market financial services or
products that we jointly offer, endorse or sponsor.
Companies under contract to perform services for us, or on our behalf, such as vendors that
prepare and mail statements and transaction confirmations or provide FX Arena data processing,
computer software maintenance and development, processing and marketing services. These
companies are acting on our behalf.
These companies, acting on our behalf, are required to keep your personal information
confidential. Also, we may disclose personal information with non-affiliated companies and
regulatory authorities as permitted or required by applicable law. For example, we may disclose
personal information to cooperate with regulatory authorities and law enforcement agencies to
comply with subpoenas or other official requests, and as necessary to protect our rights or
property. Except as described in this privacy policy, we will not use your personal information for
any other purpose unless we describe how such information will be used, at the time you disclose
it to us, or we obtain your permission to do so.
Accessing and Revisiting Your Personal
Information:
We endeavor to keep our customer files complete and accurate. We will give you reasonable
access to the information we have about you. Most of this information is contained in account
statements that you receive from us and applications that you submit to obtain our products and
services. We encourage you to review this information and notify us if you believe any information
should be corrected or updated. If you have a question or concern about your personal
information or this privacy notice, please contact us.
                                                                                                    3

CARD PROCESSING
Card processing is provided by GSL Genius Services Limited with offices at Makariou & Agias Elenis
36, Galaxias Building, 5th Floor, Office 502, 1061, Nicosia, Cyprus.
REFUNDS AND WITHDRAWALS
We reserve the right to impose withdrawal limits and withdrawal fees in our systems, at any time.
Upon submitting a withdrawal request you may be required to submit documentation as required by
applicable “Anti-Money Laundering (“AML”) & Know Your Customer (“KYC”) Legislation” and/or any
other similar rules and regulations applicable to us.
When a withdrawal or refund is performed, we reserve the right (but shall under no circumstances
be obliged) to remit the funds to the same remitter from, and by the same payment method through
which such funds were initially received by us. In that connection, we reserve the right, at our sole
discretion, (a) to decline withdrawals via certain specific payment methods; (b) to require another
payment method as the one indicated in any withdrawal request, in which instance a new withdrawal
request may have to be submitted; and/or (c) to require that further documentation be submitted, as
required by applicable “Anti-Money Laundering (“AML”) & Know Your Customer (“KYC”) Legislation”
and/or any other similar rules and regulations applicable to us, before proceeding with any withdrawal
request.
If we are unable to remit the funds, or any partial amount thereof, to the same remitter from, and by
the same payment method through which such funds were initially received by us, we reserve the
right (but shall under no circumstances be obliged) to transmit the funds via an alternative payment
method selected by us, at our sole discretion, in any currency we deem fit (regardless of the currency
in which the initial deposit was made). Under these circumstances, we shall not be responsible for
any transfer fees or charges charged by the receiver and/or for any currency exchange rates resulting
from the payment of such amount.
Withdrawal requests that are accepted and approved by us in accordance with the terms of this
Agreement are, in principle, processed within one Business Days following the receipt of the transfer
request instructions. The amount to be transferred reduces the balance of the relevant account from
which such transfer is to be made, when the transfer request process is concluded. We reserve the
right (a) to decline a withdrawal request if the request is not in accordance with the provisions of this
Section, or (b) to delay the processing of the request if we are not satisfied with the ancillary
documentation submitted with the withdrawal request.
You agree, when we so request, to pay any bank transfer fees incurred when you are withdrawing
funds from your account or when funds are refunded by us to your designated bank account. You
are solely responsible for the payments details you are providing us with and we do not accept any
                                                                                                        4

responsibility for your funds, if the payment details you have provided to us are incorrect or
incomplete. It is also understood that we do not accept any responsibility for any funds that are not
directly deposited into our bank accounts.
COMPLAINTS HANDLING PROCEDURES
1.1. As part of our commitment to providing the best possible service to our clients, we uphold
effective and transparent procedures for prompt complaint handling for existing and potential retail
clients, we maintain records of complaints and measures taken for complaint resolution, in line with
Applicable Laws, Rules and/or Regulations.
1.2. We will attempt to deal with your complaint in a prompt and efficient manner. We will follow the
procedures outlined below to ensure that your complaint is resolved within a period of thirty (30)
Business Days (where possible). Some complaints can be resolved more quickly depending on the
facts and the nature of the complaint. If the complaint is more complex and takes longer than thirty
(30) Business Days to resolve, we will communicate the reasons for the delay.
1.3. Any complaint or dispute or difference whatsoever between us, must be dealt in accordance
with the Complaint Handling Procedures set forth herein and you agree that we shall have the right
to resolve any complaint or dispute or difference whatsoever between us in accordance with the
Complaint Handling Procedures set forth herein.
How to make a complaint
1.4. Clients who wish to file a complaint must do so in writing and address it to our Complaints
Officer, at any time, via email to: complaints@fxarena.com, along with attachments of the
documentation as outlined below. All complaints will be handled by the Complaints Officer who will
independently and impartially investigate and handle the complaints, according to the procedures set
forth herein. All complaints shall be treated fairly, consistently, promptly and with confidentiality.
1.5. The following information and documentation should, wherever possible, be obtained and
recorded and provided to the Complaints Officer as part of your complaint, in order to ensure that the
complaint is expedited in the most efficient and fair manner: (a) Account Number/User ID; (b) Full
name of client; (c) Contact details and address for client; (h) Details of the complaint (including time
and date the matter leading to the complaint occurred, the representative(s) involved in the complaint;
(i) Nature of the complaint; (j) Remedies sought; (k) Attach any documentation or other material that
may assist in the resolution of the complaint (including an initial written response to the allegations
by the representative(s) involved).
                                                                                                       5

1.6. Upon receipt of a complaint, written acknowledgment will be sent to you via email within seven
(5) Business Days from the date the complaint was received. This will confirm that we are taking the
necessary action needed to resolve the complaint, and will also provide an approximate timescale
required in order to do so.
1.7. Once we have completed the complaint’s investigation, we will inform you again of the
resolution of the complaint via email and provide you a summary outcome of our investigation. Where
appropriate, it may also include a final offer of redress. Such email will be marked clearly as the final
response.
1.8. We will attempt to send the final response within thirty (30) Business Days of receiving your
complaint, or ten (10) Business Days after your acceptance or rejection of any offer of redress (where
applicable), whichever comes first. This may not always be possible as sometimes the complexity of
the complaint may require more time to investigate fully. We will always abide by regulatory
guidelines in relation to a complaint and as such, we will always ensure that complainants are kept
informed about their complaint and our activities in response to their complaint.
Monitoring of complaints
We keep detailed records on individual complaints and we maintain an internal register of complaints
where all relevant information and progress of each complaint is kept.
                                                                                                       6
